As an example, we'll start off using the belt that's here on my jacket.
Buying a jacket that comes with a belt such as this is going to give the jacket a little bit more definition in the waist and is going to give you a little bit more of a figure.
The belt that we have here is pretty versatile; this one's going to work well with jeans.
Or you might play around with it and put it over a dress...a red dress, a black dress, to give it a little bit of a waist definition.
It's going to draw the eye to that area of the body.
This is another pretty versatile belt here; it has a little extra accessory in the chain.
When you wear something such as this, make sure that your accessories match it.
So this is going to set the tone for the rest of the jewelry that you are going to be wearing....you would want to stick with silver.
Finally, we have kind of a fun belt; this one's a little bit bigger.
It's going to make the waist look smaller.
And also draw you eyes especially to that area with the shine and the silver.
This is a belt that wouldn't necessarily fit in your belt loops, but you can wear it over sweaters, over dresses, and then on the outside of a pair of pants, possibly even a high waisted pair for this one.
Join us in the next segment; we are going to be talking about hats.